A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 3, Series 15 FA1485
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants and Program Files, 1982-2012; 1
  - Healthy Steps - ICF Incorporated - Grant Products (20010115) (Box 205, Folder 1-2)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF Incorporated - Administration and Budget (20010115) (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF Incorporated - Barth - Grant Products (20020695) (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF Incorporated - Barth - Correspondence (20020695) (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF Incorporated - Barth - Administration and Budget (20020695) (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF Incorporated - Barth - Proposal Development (20020695) (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF Incorporated - Barth - Correspondence (20020695) (Box 206, Folder 2A)
  - Lieberman - Consumers Union (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - Future of Health Insurance - Findlay Papers (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Mass. DHCFP (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - Pediatric Developmental Services Program - Administration, Staff Memos, Meeting Materials (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - UCLA - Medicaid Child Development Services (980562) - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - Neal Hafron Medicaid Project (980562) - April Board 1998 (Box 206, Folder 8)
  - Medicaid and Infant Development Services (Box 207, Folder 1-2)
  - UCLA - Medicaid Child Development Services (980562) - Administration, 1998 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - UCLA - Medicaid Child Development Services (980562) - Grant Products, 1998 (Box 207, Folder 4-7)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF (20010645) - Proposal (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF (20010645) - Administration and Budget (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF (20010645) - Correspondence (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Healthy Steps - Advocate Chronicle (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF (20010645) - Overview (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Grantmakers in Health - LeRoy (20000079) - Health Issue Forums with Local Foundations, 2000 May 18 (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Healthy Steps - 30 Month Provider Instruments, 1999 (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - Book Program Products - Rockefeller University, 90-09, 1990 (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - Book Program Products - Rockefeller University, 90-61, 91-89, 1990; 1991 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - Book Program Products - Rockefeller University, 94-93, 1994 (Box 209, Folder 2-3)
  - Book Program Products, 93-52, 1993 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Book Program Products, 970315, 1997 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - Book Program Products, 980443, 1998 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Grantmakers in Health - LeRoy (20000079) - Health Issue Forums with Local Foundations, 1999-2001 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Grantmakers in Health - LeRoy (20000079) - Health Issue Forums with Local Foundations - Grant Products (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Nuffield Trust - Owen (20000219) (Box 211, Folder 2-3)
  - Johns Hopkins - Guyer (20000185) - Healthy Steps, 2000-2001 (Box 211, Folder 4-5)
  - Johns Hopkins - Guyer (20000185) - Healthy Steps, 2000-2001 (Box 212, Folder 1-4)
  - Johns Hopkins - Guyer (20000185) - Healthy Steps - Proposal (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Johns Hopkins - Guyer (20000185) - Healthy Steps - Correspondence (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Johns Hopkins - Guyer (20000185) - Healthy Steps - Grant Products, 2000-2001 (Box 213, Folder 3-4)
  - The Health Services Improvement Fund (HSIF), 1996-2000 (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - The Health Services Improvement Fund (HSIF), 1996-1998 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - The Health Services Improvement Fund (HSIF), 2000-2001 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - The Health Services Improvement Fund (HSIF), 1990-2000 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - APHSA - Partridge (990770) - State Strategies to Enhance Quality of Medicaid Managed Care - Proposal Development, 1999 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - APHSA - Partridge (990770) - State Strategies to Enhance Quality of Medicaid Managed Care - Grant Products, 1999 (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - APHSA - Partridge (990770) - State Strategies to Enhance Quality of Medicaid Managed Care - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - APHSA - Partridge (990770) - State Strategies to Enhance Quality of Medicaid Managed Care - Articles and Background, 1999 (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - APHSA - Partridge (990770) - State Strategies to Enhance Quality of Medicaid Managed Care - Administration and Budget, 1999 (Box 214, Folder 8)
  - AAHP - Bocchino (990119) - Further Assessing Effective Managed Care Practices, 1999 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Betances (20020240) (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - United Hospital Fund (20000091) (Box 215, Folder 3-4)
  - Medical and Health Research Association of New York City (MHRA) - Sandman (980786), 1998-2000 (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - Medical and Health Research Association of New York City (MHRA) - Sandman (980786), 1996-2000 (Box 216, Folder 1-2)
  - Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies Proposal, 1998 July (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies Meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 216, Folder 4-5)
  - Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies, 1997-1999 (Box 217, Folder 1-4)
  - Community Service Society, NYU (980553), 1999 (Box 218, Folder 1-2)
  - MDS Associates - Malik (980509) - Women's Health, 2000-2001 (Box 218, Folder 3-4)
  - Quality of Care for Underserved Populations Program - RFP, 2003 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Quality of Care for Underserved Populations Program - Turn-Downs, 2003 (Box 219, Folder 2-5)
  - Quality of Care for Underserved Populations Program - Turn-Downs, 2003 (Box 220, Folder 1-5)
  - Quality of Care for Underserved Populations Program - Turn-Downs, 2003 (Box 221, Folder 1-5)
  - Quality of Care for Underserved Populations Program - Turn-Downs, 2003 (Box 222, Folder 1-5)
  - Grant Reports, Articles and Updates, 1992-1996 (Box 223, Folder 1-4)
  - Grant Reports, Articles and Updates, 1997-1999 (Box 224, Folder 1-2)
  - Maternal and Child Health Policy Research Center (MCHPRC) - McManus and Fox - Medicaid Policies for Young Children (980554) - Proposal Development, 1998 (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - Maternal and Child Health Policy Research Center (MCHPRC) - McManus and Fox - Medicaid Policies for Young Children (980554) - Articles and Background, 1998 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - Maternal and Child Health Policy Research Center (MCHPRC) - McManus and Fox - Medicaid Policies for Young Children (980554) - Administration and Budget, 1998 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - Maternal and Child Health Policy Research Center (MCHPRC) - McManus and Fox - Medicaid Policies for Young Children (980554) - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Maternal and Child Health Policy Research Center (MCHPRC) - McManus and Fox - Medicaid Policies for Young Children (980554) - Grant Products, 1998-1999 (Box 225, Folder 1-4)
  - Harvard Medical School - Cleary (980467) - Quality of Care for Medicare Beneficiaries - Grant Products, 1998-1999 (Box 226, Folder 1-2)
  - International Longevity Center - Decker (20010729), 2001-2003 (Box 226, Folder 3-5)
  - Actors' Fund of America - Brown (20031315), 2003-2004 (Box 227, Folder 1-2)
  - Universal Health Care Action Network - Frisof (20031374), 2003-2004 (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University - Glied (20030133), 2002-2003 (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - Health Research and Educational Trust (HRET) - Gabel (20020163), 2001-2004 (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - Health Research and Educational Trust (HRET) - Gabel (20020163), 2001-2004 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Iowa Policy Project - Fisher (20030404), 2003-2006 (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - Employee Benefit Research Institute - Christensen (20030322), 2002-2004 (Box 228, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University - Gershon (20020264) - Bioterrorism Diseases: Training for EMS, 2002-2004 (Box 228, Folder 4-5)
  - Mathematica Policy Research - Chollet (20000511), 2000-2006 (Box 229, Folder 1-2)
  - University of Southern Maine - Coburn (20020454), 2002-2003 (Box 229, Folder 3-4)
  - University of Southern Maine - Coburn (20020454), 2002-2004 (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - Childern's Dental Health Project - Edelstein (20030546), 2002-2004 (Box 230, Folder 2-3)
  - Midwest Business Group on Health - Boress (20030437), 2003-2004 (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - Midwest Business Group on Health - Boress (20030437), 2002-2004 (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - Atlantic Health System - Scharf (20020698) (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - Atlantic Health System - Scharf (20020698) - Proposal Development (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Health System - Scharf (20020698) - Correspondence (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - Atlantic Health System - Scharf (20020698) - Grant Products (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - Atlantic Health System - Scharf (20020698) - Administration and Budget (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts College of Pharmacy - Krupat (20010417) - Exploring the Effects of Matching Physicians and Patients, 2001-2002 (Box 232, Folder 3-4)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - Riley (20010608) - Developing a Framework for Designing Mandatory Reporting Systems (Box 232, Folder 5-6)
  - Spagens and Associates - Spagens (20031439) - Replicating the Wellspring Model, 2003-2005 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - Yale - Inouye (20040073) - HELP Spreading Innovation Project, 2003-2006 (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - Yale School of Medicine - Inouye (990912) - Replicating Elder-Life Program, 1999 (Box 233, Folder 3-4)
  - Yale School of Medicine - Schlesinger (20000484) - Evaluating the Replication of the Elder-Life Program, 2000-2004 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - Yale School of Medicine - Schlesinger (20000484) - Evaluating the Replication of the Elder-Life Program, 2000-2004 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Yale School of Medicine - Schlesinger (20000484) - Evaluating the Replication of the Elder-Life Program - Grant Products, 2000-2004 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - University of Wisconsin - Bowers-Zimmerman (20020672) - Enhancing and Refining Wellspring, 2002-2004 (Box 234, Folder 3-5)
  - University of Wisconsin - Bowers-Zimmerman (20020672) - Enhancing and Refining Wellspring, 2004 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Association for Health Center Affiliated Health Plans - Murray (20040239) - Recruiting and Retaining Specialty Physicians (Box 235, Folder 2-3)
  - APHA - Benjamin (20040217) - National Public Health Week 2004 (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Foundation for Informed Decision-Making - Fowler (20031471) - Decision Aid for Breat Cancer (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - Riley (20000508), 2000-2001 (Box 235, Folder 6-7)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - Riley (20000508), 2000-2001 (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - Riley (20000508) - Proposal Development (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - Riley (20000508) - Grant Products (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - Riley (20000508) - Correspondence (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - Riley (20000508) - Administration and Budget (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - Riley (20000508) - Articles and Background (Box 236, Folder 6)
  - Harvard Medical School - Reede (20000708), 2000-2001 (Box 236, Folder 7)
  - Harvard Medical School - Reede (20000708) - Grant Products (Box 237, Folder 1-2)
  - Tufts University School of Medicine - Kaplan (20010416) - Evaluating and Addressing Methodological Challenges in Assessing Individual Physician Performance, 2001-2002 (Box 237, Folder 3-4)
  - Tufts University School of Medicine - Kaplan (20010416) - Evaluating and Addressing Methodological Challenges in Assessing Individual Physician Performance, 2001-2002 (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - Health Care Reform Briefings, 1993 (Box 238, Folder 2-4)
  - University of Rochester-Strong Memorial Hospital (96997), 1996 (Box 238, Folder 5)
  - William Carey College (92-51) - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - Commission on Women's Health - College Health (94-45), 1994-1997 (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - Harvard University School of Public Health (94-12) - HMO Networks, Managed Care - Grant Products, 1994 (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Harvard University School of Public Health (94-12) - HMO Networks, Managed Care - Administrative, 1994 (Box 239, Folder 4)
  - Harvard University School of Public Health (94-12) - HMO Networks, Managed Care - Readings, 1994 (Box 239, Folder 5)
  - Vanderbilt University (94-21) - Grant Products, 1994 (Box 239, Folder 6)
  - Multinational Health Policy Survey - Blendon - Administration and Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 239, Folder 7)
  - Multinational Health Policy Survey - Blendon, 1997-1998 (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - Women's Health Survey (93-71) - Administration and Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 240, Folder 2)
  - Committee for Economic Development (990631) - Mentoring is Good Business, 1999 (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - New York University (NYU) - Boufford (980781) - Dialogues, 1998 (Box 240, Folder 4)
  - Rice-UCLA (980773) - Understanding the Impact of Medicare Managed Care on the Medicare Medigap Market - Proposal Development, 1998-2000 (Box 240, Folder 5)
  - Rice-UCLA (980773) - Understanding the Impact of Medicare Managed Care on the Medicare Medigap Market - Administration and Budget (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Rice-UCLA (980773) - Understanding the Impact of Medicare Managed Care on the Medicare Medigap Market - Correspondence (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - Rice-UCLA (980773) - Understanding the Impact of Medicare Managed Care on the Medicare Medigap Market - Grant Products (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - The Urban Institute - Acs (990806) - The Future of Employment-Based Health Insurance, 1999-2000 (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - The Urban Institute - Acs (990806) - The Future of Employment-Based Health Insurance - Grant Products, 1999-2000 (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - Grant Reports, Articles and Updates, 1992-1994 (Box 241, Folder 6)
  - Grant Reports, Articles and Updates, 1995-2000 (Box 242, Folder 1-5)
  - Short HRS Analysis Products (990568), 1999 (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - Access for Low Income Diabetics and Asthmatics (96967) - Proposal Development, 1996-1997 (Box 243, Folder 2)
  - Access for Low Income Diabetics and Asthmatics (96967) - Articles and Background, 1996-1997 (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - Access for Low Income Diabetics and Asthmatics (96967) - Administration and Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - Access for Low Income Diabetics and Asthmatics (96967) - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 243, Folder 5)
  - Access for Low Income Diabetics and Asthmatics (96967) - Grant Products, 1996-1997 (Box 243, Folder 6)
  - George Washington University - Rosenbaum (990566) - The Role of Academic Health Centers in the Diffusion of Medical Information, 1998-1999 (Box 244, Folder 1)
  - George Washington University - First Working Group Dinner, 1999 September 21 (Box 244, Folder 2)
  - George Washington University - Rosenbaum (990566) - The Role of Academic Health Centers in the Diffusion of Medical Information - Articles and Background (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - George Washington University - Rosenbaum (990566) - The Role of Academic Health Centers in the Diffusion of Medical Information - Administration and Budget (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - George Washington University - Rosenbaum (990566) - The Role of Academic Health Centers in the Diffusion of Medical Information - Correspondence (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - George Washington University - Rosenbaum (990566) - The Role of Academic Health Centers in the Diffusion of Medical Information - Proposal Development (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - George Washington University - Rosenbaum (990566) - The Role of Academic Health Centers in the Diffusion of Medical Information - Grant Products, 1999-2001 (Box 244, Folder 7)
  - George Washington University - Rosenbaum (990566) - The Role of Academic Health Centers in the Diffusion of Medical Information - Grant Products, 1999-2001 (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - George Washington University (980772) - Medicaid Managed Care, 1998-2000 (Box 245, Folder 2-3)
  - Boston University (20000200) - LOA, Proposal, Budget (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - Boston University (20000200) - Correspondence (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - Medical and Health Research Association of New York City (MHRA), 2002 (Box 245, Folder 6)
  - Jane Perkins - Nhelp (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - New York University (NYU) - Billings (990116) - Proposal Development, 1999 (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - New York University (NYU) - Billings (990116) - Grant Products, 1999 (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Harvard University - Swartz (990773) - Proposal Development, 1999 (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Harvard University - Swartz (990773) - Grant Products, 1999 (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Harvard University - Swartz (990773) - Articles and Background, 1999 (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - Harvard University - Swartz (990773) - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures (NCSL), 2000-2003 (Box 247, Folder 1-3)
  - Prottas (20030030) - The Access Project, 2002-2003 (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Prottas (20030030) - The Access Project, 2002-2003 (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - Foundation Center - Englehardt (20010438) (Box 248, Folder 2)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth and Families - Renwanz (20020575), 2002-2003 (Box 248, Folder 3)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth and Families - Renwanz (20010439) (Box 248, Folder 4)
  - Health Services Association of Australia and New Zealand - Chinchen (20020569), 2001-2003 (Box 248, Folder 5)
  - Health Services Association of Australia and New Zealand - Chinchen (20030519) (Box 248, Folder 6)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers - Bryan (20020513) (Box 248, Folder 7)
  - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York - Small (20030521) (Box 248, Folder 8)
  - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York - Small (20020514), 2001-2002 (Box 248, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller University - Stapleton (20031373), 2003-2004 (Box 248, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller University - Stapleton (20020663) (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers - Bryan (20030520), 2002-2003 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Foundation Center - Englehardt (20020524), 2001-2003 (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - Grantmakers in Aging - Farquhar (20020567), 2002-2003 (Box 249, Folder 4)
  - Grantmakers in Aging - Farquhar (20030517) (Box 249, Folder 5)
  - Grantmakers in Aging - Farquhar (20010344), 2001-2002 (Box 249, Folder 6)
  - Grantmakers in Aging - Greenberg (990577), 1998-1999 (Box 249, Folder 7)
  - Grantmakers in Aging (20040528), 2004-2005 (Box 249, Folder 8)
  - Grantmakers in Health - LeRoy (20030518), 2002-2003 (Box 249, Folder 9)
  - Grantmakers in Health - LeRoy (20010440) (Box 249, Folder 10)
  - Grantmakers in Health - LeRoy (20020574), 2002-2003 (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth and Families - Bogie (990535), 1999 (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - Grantmakers in Aging (20000517), 2000-2003 (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth and Families - Renwanz (20000532), 1999-2000 (Box 250, Folder 4)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute - Silow-Carroll (20050203) (Box 250, Folder 5)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute - Doran (20040718), 2004-2006 (Box 251, Folder 1-2)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (20020508) (Box 251, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (20020508) - Proposal Development (Box 251, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (20020508) - Grant Products (Box 251, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (20020508) - Grant Products (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (20020508) - Correspondence (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth Fund Business Colloquium, 2002 November 18 (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Fairbrother (20040440), 2004-2005 (Box 252, Folder 4)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Fairbrother (20040440) - Correspondence, Grant Documents (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Fairbrother (20040440) - Proposal Development (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute - Dorn (20050463), 2005-2006 (Box 253, Folder 2)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute - Dorn (20031342), 2003-2007 (Box 253, Folder 3)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute - Dorn (20031342) - Proposal Development (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute - Dorn (20031342) - Grant Products (Box 253, Folder 5)
  - Georgetown College - Mann (20040441) - Unstable Health Insurance, 2004-2005 (Box 254, Folder 1-2)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - Kaye (20040339) - Using Evidence-Based Medicine to Control Pharmaceutical Program Costs, Phase 1, 2004-2005 (Box 254, Folder 3)
  - Center for Health Policy Development - Kaye (20040339) - Using Evidence-Based Medicine to Control Pharmaceutical Program Costs, Phase 1 - Proposal Development, 2003-2005 (Box 254, Folder 4)
  - Rutgers - Crystal (20000709) - Experience of State Pharmaceutical Assistance Programs, 2000-2003 (Box 255, Folder 1)
  - Rutgers - Crystal (20000709) - Experience of State Pharmaceutical Assistance Programs - Budget and Administration (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Rutgers - Crystal (20000709) - Experience of State Pharmaceutical Assistance Programs - Correspondence (Box 255, Folder 3)
  - Rutgers - Crystal (20000709) - Experience of State Pharmaceutical Assistance Programs - Proposal Development (Box 255, Folder 4)
  - Rutgers - Crystal (20000709) - Experience of State Pharmaceutical Assistance Programs - Grant Products, 2002-2003 (Box 255, Folder 5-7)
  - Rutgers - Crystal (20000709) - Experience of State Pharmaceutical Assistance Programs - Grant Products, 2000-2002 (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Pronovost (20020637) - Evaluating the Response to Leapfrog Group's Standard for Intensive Care Unit Staffing, 2002-2005 (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Pronovost (20020637) - Evaluating the Response to Leapfrog Group's Standard for Intensive Care Unit Staffing - Administration and Budget (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Pronovost (20020637) - Evaluating the Response to Leapfrog Group's Standard for Intensive Care Unit Staffing - Correspondence (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Pronovost (20020637) - Evaluating the Response to Leapfrog Group's Standard for Intensive Care Unit Staffing - Articles and Background (Box 256, Folder 5)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Pronovost (20020637) - Evaluating the Response to Leapfrog Group's Standard for Intensive Care Unit Staffing - Grant Products (Box 256, Folder 6)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Pronovost (20020637) - Evaluating the Response to Leapfrog Group's Standard for Intensive Care Unit Staffing - Proposal Development (Box 256, Folder 7)
  - Community Catalyst - Sherry (20030403) - The Small Business and Non-Group Health Insurance Project, 2003-2005 (Box 257, Folder 1-2)
  - DMA Health Strategies - Dougherty (20060055), 2005-2006 (Box 257, Folder 3)
  - Lewin Group - Alecxih (990480), 1999-2002 (Box 257, Folder 4)
  - Lewin Group - Alecxih (990480) - Grant Products (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - Lewin Group - Alecxih (990480) - Administration and Budget (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Lewin Group - Alecxih (990480) - Articles and Background (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - Lewin Group - Alecxih (990480) - Proposal Development (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - Lewin Group - Alecxih (990480) - Correspondence (Box 258, Folder 4)
  - Regents of the University of California - Kronick (20010688) - Estimating the Effects of Health Insurance on the Health and Financial Security of Working Adults, 2001-2003 (Box 258, Folder 5)
  - Regents of the University of California - Kronick (20010688) - Estimating the Effects of Health Insurance on the Health and Financial Security of Working Adults - Proposal Development (Box 258, Folder 6)
  - Center for the Advancement of Health - Lefkowitz (20020531) - Heroes of Community Health, 2002-2007 (Box 258, Folder 7)
  - National Alliance for Hispanic Health - Falcon (20030227) - Mobilizing Hispanic Community Leaders for A Hispanic Health Insurance Agenda, 2003-2006 (Box 259, Folder 1)